Fast food executive Jim Ferguson stepped out of his 47th floor office to go to the bathroom...
and ended up in the middle of World War I. History will be grateful forever.
Biggles is a action, family, fantasy film directed by John Hough.
Unassuming catering salesmen Jim Ferguson falls through a time hole to 1917 where he saves the life of dashing
Royal Flying Corps pilot James "Biggles" Bigglesworth after his photo recon mission is shot down.
Before he can work out what has happened, Jim is zapped back to the 1980s......
James 'Biggles' Bigglesworth, played by Neil Dickson.
Jim Ferguson, played by Alex Hyde-White.
Debbie, played by Fiona Hutchison.
Air Commodore Colonel William Raymond, played by Peter Cushing.
Eric Von Stalhein, played by Marcus Gilbert.
Chuck, played by William Hootkins.
Biggles is a 1986 British science fiction adventure film directed by John Hough
(released in 1988 in the United States as Biggles: Adventures in Time).
The plot involves time travel between the 1980s and the First World War,
involving the character, Biggles (from the series of novels by W.
The film stars Neil Dickson, Alex Hyde-White, and Peter
Cushing in his final feature film role.
The film explores themes of world war i, time travel, twin brother, fighter ace.
The tone is thought_provoking.